(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
この後、ラプラスさんの生誕祭があるらしいんですけど...
It seems there's a birthday festival for La+ after this...
(ラプラスの生誕祭は) 割とレベルの高い合格点を超える生誕祭をオールウェイズ出してくれる
(La+'s birthday festivals) always deliver performances that exceed a fairly high passing grade.
どこから来たんですか？
Where did you come from?
えっと、あの、スト6の方から
Um, from Street Fighter 6.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
開会してるんでしょ？
It's opening, isn't it?
閉会しています！
It's closing!
開会してんでしょ？
It's opening, right?
閉会してます。
It's closing.
さっき開会してるって言ったじゃん。
You just said it was opening.
閉会しています！
It's closing!
ラプラス・ダークネスの生誕祭は...
La+ Darknesss's birthday festival is...
閉会しています！
Closing!
みんな！吾輩の誕生日ライブに来てくれてありがとね！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to my birthday live!
まずは1曲目！夜行性ハイズ！
First song! 'Nocturnal Highs'!
イクゾー！
Let's go!
勝ち誇って忘れてたい　そんな顔でいつまで戦うの
I want to forget while gloating; how long will you fight with that face?
また一人で
Once again, alone.
愛しても愛しても　その度に傷口が顔を出す
No matter how much I love, the wounds show their face every time.
巻き戻すように
As if rewinding.
どうして一から十まで更には百まで飲み込む苦しみだけは　なくなってくれないの
Why is it that only the pain I swallow—from one to ten, even to a hundred—won't go away?
総じて逃げ場もないのにマイナス一から始まる同期の日々も　各々...
Though there's no escape overall, the days of synchronization starting from minus one, each...
描けないや
I can't draw it.
ちょっと泣いて
Cry a little,
無理もしたら
and if you push yourself,
ここへおいでよ　いつだって
come here anytime.
これからの話をしようか
Shall we talk about the future?
眠たいが寝ない　まだ境界
I'm sleepy but won't sleep, still at the boundary.
僕ら何度だって想い合ったって言うんだよ
We say we've felt for each other over and over again.
傷ついたっていい　見たいから
It's okay to get hurt, because I want to see.
なんかハイな声が丁度いいやって泣いちゃって
Somehow a high voice is just right, and I end up crying.
死にたいも消えたいも　異常じゃない
Neither wanting to die nor wanting to disappear is abnormal.
よしよしして　水際でほら弾けちゃおう
There, there, let's pop at the water's edge.
君は泣いたって綺麗だよ
You are beautiful even when you cry.
さらば　あっち向いて前向いて笑ってこうじゃない？　もう
Farewell, shouldn't we look that way, look forward and laugh? Already.
寂しくない　悲しくない
I'm not lonely, I'm not sad.
塗り重ねた強がり深呼吸洗い流せたら
If I could wash away the layers of bluffing with a deep breath.
バイバイを　バイバイを
Bye bye, bye bye.
馬鹿みたいな世界にありがとう　探さないでね
Thank you to this foolish world, don't look for me.
そして僕らは　広くも狭くも熱くも寒くもないこの部屋で
And so we hold hands and breathe in this room that is
手を取り合って息をするの
neither wide nor narrow, hot nor cold.
常識外れを外れて二人だけの合言葉で鍵をかけたら
Deviating from common sense, if we lock up with our secret code,
さぁどんな夜をしようか
well, what kind of night shall we have?
だけど痛い　だから痛い
But it hurts, that's why it hurts.
優しさが染み込んでいく
Kindness is soaking in.
消息を始めようか
Shall we start our disappearance?
眠たいが寝ない　まだ境界
I'm sleepy but won't sleep, still at the boundary.
声を何度だって送り合って保ってきましたが
I've kept it up by sending my voice over and over again, but...
やめよう　逃げよう　大丈夫だよ
Let's stop, let's run away, it's okay.
もう寝たっていい　ちゃんと僕が守ってあげるから
It's okay to sleep now, because I'll protect you properly.
おはようをしよう　また今日にしよう
Let's say good morning, let's make it today again.
よしよしして　水際でほら弾けちゃおう
There, there, let's pop at the water's edge.
僕も泣いちゃってヤバイから
Because I'm also crying and it's bad.
さらば　あっち向いて前向いて笑ってこうじゃない？
Farewell, shouldn't we look that way, look forward and laugh?
弱虫な僕たちは
We, who are cowards,
回っても　回ってな
even if we go around, keep going around.
終わらない今日も吐いて　光ってく
Breathing out the never-ending today, shining.
辛いのは辛いけど
Being hard is hard, but
二人で乗り越えるさ
we'll overcome it together.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
えーとね、まだまだ続くから
Um, there's still more to come,
めちゃくちゃ楽しんでいってねー！
so please enjoy it to the fullest!
バイバーイ、バイバーイ、バイバーイ、バイバーイ！
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye bye!
今度、ラプラスさんの生誕祭があるらしいんですけど
I heard there's going to be a birthday event for La+ soon.
ええ！マジですか！？ あの、え、ラプラスさんってあのホロライブの！？
Whoa! Seriously!? Um, eh, La+ as in the one from Hololive!?
僕、あの、アレ、待ち受けにしてるんですよ
I, uh, have that, as my wallpaper.
しかも今回のハッシュタグが #ラプラス・バースデイ2025 らしくて
And apparently the hashtag for this time is #LaplusBirthday2025.
えー！マジでショックです...
Whaaat! I'm seriously shocked...
でも、幸せならOKです！
But if she's happy, it's okay!
ねぇあたしのことが好きなら　気付いて気付いて気付いて気付いて
Hey, if you love me, notice me, notice me, notice me, notice me.
夢を見させてよ
Let me dream.
どうして分かってくれないの　嫌いだ嫌いだ嫌いだ嫌いだ
Why don't you understand? I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
二度と触れないで
Don't ever touch me again.
パラサイト 作詞・作曲：DECO*27
Parasite / Lyrics & Music: DECO*27
ちょっと待ってどこからおかしくなったの
Wait a minute, where did it start to go wrong?
ダメなとこも好きになれてよかったのに
I was glad that I could even come to love your bad parts.
バッとのんで誰かに埋めてもらえたら
If I could just drink it down and have someone fill the void,
あなたのこと忘れられると思いたかった
I wanted to think I could forget about you.
キモがって都合よくなければ繋がってるなら悪くはないね
It's not bad if we're connected, as long as it's not creepy or just for convenience.
騙し騙し生きてきちゃって
Living a life of deception.
優しくされると余計に辛いけど冷たくされるの望んでないよ
It's even more painful when you're kind, but I don't want you to be cold either.
あたしだけでいいって信じちゃって　バカだ
Believing that I'm the only one... I'm an idiot.
ねぇあたしのことが好きなら　気付いて気付いて気付いて気付いて
Hey, if you love me, notice me, notice me, notice me, notice me.
夢を見させてよ
Let me dream.
どうして分かってくれないの　嫌いだ嫌いだ嫌いだ嫌いだ
Why don't you understand? I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
二度と触れないで
Don't ever touch me again.
1, 2, 3で流れ星　あの子のこと
One, two, three, a shooting star... about that girl...
…なら呪ってあげるわ
...then I'll put a curse on you.
ねえ、足元からお返ししてよ
Hey, pay me back from the ground up.
嘘つき、嘘つき、嘘つき、嘘つき
Liar, liar, liar, liar.
って、ものが好きだよ
...is what I love.
手吸って、吐いて
Breathe in, breathe out.
そう、ちゃんと生きて
That's it, live properly.
細く舐める愛の子だとか躾けず煙るそうだよ
They say it's like a child of love being licked thin, smoky without being tamed.
ねえ、置いてかないで
Hey, don't leave me behind.
ねえ、お腹空いた
Hey, I'm hungry.
見て、ねえ唾を吐いて
Look, hey, spit out.
燃えないゴミにするんだ
I'll turn it into non-combustible waste.
何で？何で？何で？何で？何で？
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
ねえ、私のことが好きなら
Hey, if you love me,
気づいて、気づいて、気づいて、気づいて
Notice me, notice me, notice me, notice me.
夢を見せてよ
Show me a dream.
どうして分かってくれないの？
Why won't you understand me?
嫌いだ、嫌いだ、嫌いだ、嫌いだ
I hate you, I hate you, I hate you, I hate you.
大嫌いだ
I hate you so much.
もう、あなたは振り向かないの？
Won't you ever look back?
気づいてる、気づいてる、気づいてる、気づいてる
I know, I know, I know, I know.
どうして放っておけないの？
Why can't you leave me alone?
死にたいよ、死にたいよ、死にたいよ、死にたいよ
I want to die, I want to die, I want to die, I want to die.
離れたくないよ
I don't want to leave.
正解状は、一、二の、三で
The answer sheet, on one, two, three,
流れ星、あのこのこと
A shooting star, about that girl,
呪ってあげるわ
I'll put a curse on her.
ねえ、最後にキスをさせて欲しい
Hey, I want you to let me kiss you one last time.
ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがとう
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
これであなたも
Now you're also...
ラプラス・ファンは──
La+ fans are...
次のラプラスさんの曲アンドロイドガールらしいんですけど
I heard La+’s next song is 'Android Girl'...
えー、何すか？
Huh, what?
それは許せないと思います、これ
I don't think that's acceptable, this.
「テメェらバカかよ！」というのが第一ですね
'Are you guys stupid?!' is my first reaction.
ラプラスといえば、"アイドル"みたいなものですからね
When it comes to La+, she’s like an 'idol,' you know?
それはちょっと、世間は許してくれませんよ
Well, the public won't stand for that.
アンドロイドガール
作詞・作曲：DECO*27
Android Girl
Lyrics/Composition: DECO*27
おい、一生、楽を作りましょう
Hey, let's make a life of ease.
君とマッチアップの過程
The process of matching up with you.
構って、もっと、足りないの
Pay attention to me more, it's not enough.
甘い思い出染み出したこのスタイル
This style that exudes sweet memories.
変わる、変わる、傷つけては
Change, change, and by hurting,
もったいないって嘘で泣かなおりごっこだ
it's a game of making up with a lie that it's a waste.
勘違いの騙し合い
A mutual deception born of misunderstanding.
目を見ればすぐに分かって馬鹿みたい
If you look into my eyes, you'll know right away, how stupid.
妄想にふけるほど
The more I indulge in delusions,
この愛は腐ってるんだよ
this love is rotting away.
早く気づいてくれよ
Please, realize it soon.
アンドロイドガールおかしくなっちゃった
Android Girl has gone crazy.
僕だけのものになった君は誰なの？
Who are you, you who have become mine alone?
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、信じてきたのにな
I believed in you all this time.
アンドロイドガール、思い出したっけ
Android Girl, did you remember?
君とのキスがいって、息を閉じたの
Your kiss hurt, and I stopped breathing.
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、何万回を再起したって
No matter how many tens of thousands of times I restart,
ちょっとだけ変われだの知らないよ
I don't care if you've changed just a little bit.
あぁ、可愛いい眼、どうしてくれよ
Ah, those cute eyes, what should I do?
もう、疲れた、ドキドキさせるサイズ感
I'm tired of the heart-pounding size of it all.
うざい、うざいの並行罪
Annoying, annoying parallel guilt.
期待しているか分からなくなったよ
I don't know if I'm still expecting anything.
エンドロールはまだですか？
Is it the end credits yet?
どこに行っても一緒だ、なんてマジで言いたい
I really want to say it's the same wherever I go.
干渉に浸っていたら
If I'm immersed in sentimentality,
あの頃を願っていたら
if I'm wishing for those days,
ありがた、まじか、教えてよ
Is it a blessing? Really? Tell me.
アンドロイドガールおかしくなっちゃった
Android Girl has gone crazy.
君だけのものになった僕が好きなの？
Do you love me, I who have become yours alone?
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、騙してきたんだね
You've been deceiving me all this time.
アンドロイドガール、思い出したっけ
Android Girl, did you remember?
錆びついた腕で何回も僕を求めた
You reached for me countless times with your rusted arms.
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、何万回を再起したって
No matter how many tens of thousands of times I restart,
ちょっとだけ変われだの知らないよ
I don't care if you've changed just a little bit.
アンドロイドガールおかしくなっちゃった
Android Girl has gone crazy.
僕だけのものになった君は誰なの？
Who are you, you who have become mine alone?
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、信じてきたのにな
I believed in you all this time.
アンドロイドガール、思い出したっけ
Android Girl, did you remember?
君とのキスがいって、息を閉じたの
Your kiss hurt, and I stopped breathing.
ずっと
Always.
ずっと、お邪魔なまま離れない
Always, staying in the way, never leaving.
君だけは許さない
I won't forgive only you.
アンドロイドガールおかしくなっちゃった
Android Girl has gone crazy.
君だけのものになった僕が好き、ずっと...
I like myself for becoming yours alone, forever...
...ずっと騙してきたんだね
...you've been deceiving me all along.
アンドロイドガール 思いはなんだっけ
Android girl, what were your feelings again?
錆びついた腕で何十回僕を求めた
How many dozen times did you seek me with rusted arms?
ずっと ずっと
Forever and ever
何度愛を再起動したって
No matter how many times I reboot love
ちょっとだって変われなどしねえ
It doesn't change even a little bit
ああ 何度愛を再起動したって
Ah, no matter how many times I reboot love
ちょっとだって変われなどしねえや
It doesn't change even a little bit
ホロライブ一影が薄い ラプラス・ダークネス
Hololive's most overshadowed member, La+ Darknesss
ラプラス・ダークネスは―
La+ Darknesss is—
ホロライブでラプラスさんの影が薄いというお話なんですが...
So there's talk about you being overshadowed in Hololive...
いや、納得できないね
No, I can't accept that.
Q ラプラスさんの魅力は？
Q: What is La+'s charm?
ラプラスさんの魅力は？
What is your charm?
ないんだな、それが
There isn't any, actually.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー / 作詞・作曲: kemu
Dear Doppelganger / Lyrics & Composition: kemu
どうもこんにちは君の分身です
Hello, I'm your doppelganger.
何の冗談か目をこすってみる
I rub my eyes, wondering what kind of joke this is.
影が二つ延びて
Two shadows stretch out,
そしてまたまじわる
And then they intersect again.
もう一人自分がいたらなんて貴方は言いました
You said, "If only there were another me."
そんな真摯な願いが僕を呼んだのさ
That sincere wish is what called me.
そりゃ願ったとも 艱難すべてのエイジェ
Sure, I wished for it, all the agents of hardship...
過程はいいから結果を下さい
Forget the process, just give me the results.
意味のない代価に
In exchange for a meaningless price.
ねえこんなことより大事なことがあるんだよ
Hey, there are more important things than this.
いいだろ？
Right?
「ええ、やりますやります 何でもやります」
“Yes, I'll do it, I'll do anything.”
「僕は君の分身です」
“I'm your doppelganger.”
含み笑いで救済はユウ
Salvation comes with a chuckle for you.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は 君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you?
ああ 混濁を指して 僕は誰？
Ah, pointing to the muddle, who am I?
ねえ ありもしないけど
Hey, it doesn't even exist,
透明の境界線 さあ 鳴らして
But ring the invisible boundary line.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 誰は 誰は君？
Dear Doppelganger, who is you?
蝕みあわれた存在に
To the presence being eaten away,
世が気付かないね なり止まない
The world won't notice, it won't stop ringing.
惨めな輪廻を越えて 世界を染め上げろ
Beyond this wretched cycle, stain the world.
ババッ
Ba-ba!
どうも様子がおかしい月曜日
Monday's looking a bit strange.
一つずつ崩れゆく辻褄が
One by one, the consistency crumbles,
僕を支配する お前は一体誰だと
Controlling me, asking "Who on earth are you?"
ちょっと待って 知らない身に覚えのない言葉
Hold on, these are unfamiliar words I don't recall.
そうやっていつの間にやら影は解けていく
And just like that, the shadow dissolves.
僕は誰だろう ねえ
Who am I? Hey,
どこか存在を返して
Give me back my existence somewhere.
アイツの方がずっとずっと好都合だって
That guy is way more convenient,
もはや居場所はここにはないこと分かってるんでしょう
You know there's no place for you here anymore, right?
ねえ 奪われたなら 奪い返せばいいだろう
Hey, if it was taken, you should just take it back.
今度はお前の番だぞ
Now it's your turn.
含み笑いでインベーダーはユウ
The invader comes with a chuckle for you.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は 君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you?
ああ 混濁を指して 僕は誰？
Ah, pointing to the muddle, who am I?
まあ それもそっか
Well, I guess that makes sense.
命の椅子は一つだけ
There's only one seat for life.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 誰は 誰は君？
Dear Doppelganger, who is you?
蝕みあわれた存在に
To the presence being eaten away,
今日が気果てる前に 誰でもいい
Before today ends, anyone will do,
何でもいい
Anything will do.
器をください 狂った世界を染め上げろ
Give me a vessel, stain this crazy world.
ババッ
Ba-ba!
それは ずっと続く 人のボウレイさ
It's an eternal human ghost.
願ったって 嬉しがったって 離れゆく
Wishing and rejoicing, yet it drifts away.
欠けたピース 懐かしの景色もまた愛も
The missing piece, nostalgic scenery, and even love,
渡し合って 生まれ変わる 永唱
Passing them back and forth, reborn in a long chant.
僕の方が ちゃんと君を生きてやるから
I'll live your life properly for you.
君も 次の誰か ちゃんと吸わなくちゃ
So you've gotta suck the life out of the next person.
もう分かってるんだろう 何をすればいいかさ
You already know what you have to do, don't you?
どうか 誰か僕に 奇跡をくれ
Please, someone give me a miracle.
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー 君は 君は誰？
Dear Doppelganger, who are you?
ああ 混濁を指して 僕は誰？
Ah, pointing to the muddle, who am I?
もう止まらない
It won't stop anymore,
戻れない どうもこんにちは君の...
There's no going back. Hello, I'm your...
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー それは それは僕？
Dear Doppelganger, is that me?
蝕みあわれた存在に
To the presence being eaten away,
世界が気付こうが もう鳴り止まない
Even if the world notices, it won't stop ringing.
惨めな輪廻を越えて 世界を染め上げるさ
Beyond this wretched cycle, I'll stain the world.
うまくやれよ
Good luck with it.
ババッ
Ba-ba!
拝啓ドッペルゲンガー
Dear Doppelganger
どうもこんにちは君の分身です
Hello, I'm your doppelganger.
うわあああああああ！
Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
うわあ！
Waaa!
紗痲
作詞・作曲：煮ル果実
Shama
Lyrics/Music: Niru Kajitsu
邪な通う執事ファム・ファタール
A wicked, frequenting butler, a femme fatale
嘘も搾りジュースは青　夜な夜な夜な
Even lies are squeezed into blue juice, night after night after night
火遊びで遺志する　常套の露が解ける頃
Leaving a will by playing with fire, when the usual dew dissolves
違和感が残業している　空気がぐじゃぐじゃしている
Discomfort is working overtime, the air is all messed up
淡々と頭垂れて　お生に入るわって
Bowing my head indifferently, saying I'm entering life
健幸いってサレンダー　お利口お利口
Saying health and happiness, then surrender, good girl, good girl
適宜的にポジ織り願おたら
If I wish for positivity in an appropriate manner
患う愛を愛と呼べんなら　如何せん僕は古みたい
If I can't call this ailing love "love", then I guess I'm like an old thing
話したいことも無いっていうから　そこで御臨終だ気づいたの？
Since you say there's nothing to talk about, you're dead right there, did you realize?
患う君を肯定したんなら　僕の居場所はどこへやら
If I affirmed the ailing you, where would my place be?
じれったい針とファンデーション　舌を曝け出して収まっている
Irritating needles and foundation, sticking my tongue out and settling in
邪な通う執事ファム・ファタール
A wicked, frequenting butler, a femme fatale
嘘も搾りジュースは青　夜な夜な夜な
Even lies are squeezed into blue juice, night after night after night
火遊びで遺志する　常套の露が解ける頃
Leaving a will by playing with fire, when the usual dew dissolves
自称天秤は　おつむが軽い方に軍配を上げた
The self-proclaimed scales gave the win to the one with the lighter head
デカダンに唆した手出しを持ってない
I don't have the hand that enticed with decadence
不潔　手脂のように追い堕したか
Filth, did you drive it away like hand grease?
患う愛を愛と呼べんなら　如何せん僕は古みたい
If I can't call this ailing love "love", then I guess I'm like an old thing
話したいわけが無いっていうけど　気付かないわけもないだろうな
You say there's no way you want to talk, but there's no way you won't notice
患う僕の存在理由はさ　患い向き合う愛の影
My reason for existing in this ailing state is the shadow of love I face
腐らんで徒に擦ったなら　しどろもどろになってたわ　もう待って
If I rubbed it in vain without rotting, I'd be all flustered, wait already
患う愛を愛と呼べんなら　如何せん僕は古みたい
If I can't call this ailing love "love", then I guess I'm like an old thing
放さないことも無いっていうから　そこで御臨終だ気づいたの？
Since you say it's not like I won't let go, you're dead right there, did you realize?
患う愛を愛と呼ぶんなら　如何せん僕が嫌みたい
If you call this ailing love "love", then I guess I'm the one who's disliked
終わりのキスも何杯目？　横縞見透かされて収まっている
How many final kisses has it been? My ulterior motives are seen through, and I'm settling in
収まっているさ
Settling in.
たけー... スタジオ寒いんだよ
It's so... the studio is cold.
ちょっと寒すぎんだろ、このスタジオ、カバーのスタジオは...
It's a bit too cold, this studio, Cover's studio is...
え？ たけー... 意味が分からない。
Eh? It's so... I don't understand.
ふざけやがって。
Stop messing with me.
椅子は竹串...
The seats are bamboo skewers...
てめえか！
Is it you?!
てめえかよ！ え？ その腐った根性！
Is it you?! Eh? That rotten spirit of yours!
笑ったね？
You laughed, didn't you?
その心笑ってるね？
You're laughing in your heart, aren't you?
悪いけどね、あんたよりよっぽど生きてるんだよ！
I'm sorry to say, but I'm much more alive than you are!
吾輩は...
I...
もっと生きてんだよ！
want to live more!
おい！
Hey!
最後までちゃんと見るって言って！
Say you'll watch until the very end!
配信最後までちゃんと見るって言って！
Say you'll watch the stream until the very end!
あー！
Aaaah!
僕がずっと前から思ってることを話そうか
Shall I tell you what I've been thinking about for a long time?
友達に戻れたらこれ以上は望まないさ
If we could go back to being friends, I wouldn't ask for anything more.
君がそれでいいなら僕だってそれで構わないさ
If you're okay with that, then I'm okay with it too.
嘘つきの僕が吐いた反対言葉の愛のうた
A love song of opposite words sung by a liar like me.
天ノ弱
作詞・作曲: 164
Amanojaku
Lyrics/Composition: 164
今日はとてもいい天気でした どしゃ降りになっていたんでした
It was very nice weather today, it was a downpour.
昨日もずっと暇で 一日満喫してました
I was free all day yesterday and enjoyed my day to the fullest.
別に君のことなんて 考えてなんていないさ
It's not like I was thinking about you or anything.
いやでもちょっと本当は 考えていたかもなんてね
Well, maybe I actually was thinking about you a little, just kidding.
メリーゴーランドみたいに回る 僕の頭ん中がもうグルグルさ
Spinning like a merry-go-round, my head is already going round and round.
この両手から零れそうなほど 君にもらった愛はどこに捨てよう？
Where should I throw away the love I got from you that's overflowing from these hands?
限りのある消耗品なんて僕は いらないよ
I don't need such limited consumables.
僕がずっと前から思ってることを話そうか
Shall I tell you what I've been thinking about for a long time?
姿は見えないのに言葉だけ見えちゃってるんだ
Even though I can't see your figure, I can see only your words.
僕が知らないことがあるだけで 気が狂いそうだ
Just the thought that there are things I don't know makes me feel like I'm going crazy.
ぶら下がった感情が綺麗なのか汚いのか
Whether these dangling emotions are beautiful or ugly,
僕にはまだわからず 捨てるあてもないんだ
I still don't know, and I have nowhere to throw them away.
言葉の裏の裏が見えるまで待つからさ
I'll wait until I can see the back of the back of your words,
真っ暗な中じゃなきゃいけないじゃないか
Because it has to be in pitch black, doesn't it?
進む君と止まった僕の 縮まらない隙間を何で埋めよう？
What should I fill the gap with that won't narrow between you who moves forward and me who stopped?
まだ素直に言葉にできない僕は 天性の弱虫さ
I, who still can't put my feelings honestly into words, am a natural coward.
この両手から零れそうなほど 君に渡す愛を誰に譲ろう？
To whom should I give the love I'm meant to give you that's overflowing from these hands?
そんな所にも宛てがあるわけないから
Because there's no way there's a destination for it there either.
まだ 待つよ
I'll still wait.
もう いいかい
Are you ready yet?
のりあきさんが歌ってるｗ
Noriaki-san is singing! lol
あー...疲れた...
Aaah... I'm tired...
気まぐれメルシィ
作詞: 八王子P/q*Left / 作曲: 八王子P
Kimagure Mercy
Lyrics: Hachioji-P/q*Left / Composition: Hachioji-P
ほらほら また始まった お得意の自己弁護言い訳
Look, look, it's starting again—your specialty: self-defense and excuses.
でもね
But you see...
だって
Because...
ほらほら また始まった ごめんからのキスのパターンって感じ
Look, look, it's starting again—the 'sorry, then a kiss' pattern.
安易
So simplistic.
いつかあたしだけ そんな夢見たこともあったけど
There was a time when I dreamed of being the only one for you...
寂しい時だけ電話して もううんざりだわ
But you only call when you're lonely. I'm so sick of it.
全然あたしに興味ないじゃん 君が好きなのは自分自身でしょ
You have zero interest in me, do you? The only one you love is yourself.
YEAH!
やっぱりあたしに興味ないじゃん その話もう聞き飽きたわ
Just as I thought, you don't care about me. I've heard that story enough.
そもそも大体あたしに興味ないじゃん そうやってまた誤魔化して
To begin with, you're not interested in me at all. You're just dodging it again.
Be my boy わがまま過ぎる baby
Be my boy, you're far too selfish, baby.
抱きしめてよ
Just hold me.
ほんときにはしょうもないな 甘やかしちゃしょうがないな 泣いたっていかないでっていったってかわらしなよ
Honestly, it's so hopeless. I can't help spoiling you. Even if I cry or say 'don't go,' just keep being charming.
もう少しだけなら まぁ踊ってもいいかもな 蕩けて溶けていたいよ
If it's just for a little longer, I guess I could dance. I want to melt away with you.
どんなアピールも意味ないし 気付いてくれないけど
No matter how I try to appeal to you, it's meaningless; you never notice.
あたしが寂しい時だって 会いに来て
But even when I'm the one feeling lonely, please come see me.
全然あたしに興味ないじゃん どこが駄目なの教えてよ
You have zero interest in me, do you? Tell me, what's wrong with me?
やっぱりあたしに興味ないじゃん 携帯ばかりいじってさ
Just as I thought, you don't care about me. Always messing with your phone.
そもそも大体あたしに興味ないじゃん 少しぐらい期待させて
To begin with, you're not interested in me at all. At least give me a little hope.
Lonely girl 独り占めしてよ baby
Lonely girl, keep me all to yourself, baby.
振り回さないで
Don't toy with my heart.
ねぇ maybe melody One, two, shall we dance? 踊りましょう
Hey, maybe a melody—one, two, shall we dance? Let's dance together.
早く手繋いで 最後にとっておきだけ 溺れるくらい愛してよ
Hurry, take my hand. Just for the very end, love me so much that I feel like I'm drowning.
全然あたしに興味ないじゃん 君が好きなのは自分自身でしょ
You have zero interest in me, do you? The only one you love is yourself.
やっぱりあたしに興味ないじゃん その話もう聞き飽きたわ
Just as I thought, you don't care about me. I've heard that story enough.
そもそも大体あたしに興味ないじゃん そうやってまた誤魔化して
To begin with, you're not interested in me at all. You're just dodging it again.
Get down, star 覚悟はできてるの?
Get down, star. Are you ready for this?
気まぐれメルシィ
Kimagure Mercy
お代はいかが?
How's that for the price?
おまえの苦労はずっと見ていたぞ
I've been watching your hard work this whole time.
本当によく頑張ったな
You've really done your best.
ついに我慢が報われ、膨大な富を得る
Finally, your patience will be rewarded, and you will gain immense wealth.
このライブを飛ばしてしまえば、これまでの苦労は全て水の泡だ
If you skip this live stream, all your past efforts will be in vain.
世界中がおまえを否定しても、吾輩だけはおまえを認めてやる
Even if the whole world rejects you, I alone will acknowledge you.
散々苦しんだのだ、もう楽になれ
You've suffered so much; now, find peace.
富を望んでいるのなら、やることがある
If you desire wealth, there is something you must do.
このライブを最後まで見てチャンネルを登録するんだ
Watch this live stream until the end and subscribe to the channel.
やり方は簡単だ、誰にでもできる
The method is simple; anyone can do it.
下の赤いチャンネル登録ボタンを押して高評価ボタンを押すのだ
Press the red subscribe button below and click the like button.
これで幸福の精算が始まる
With this, the tallying of your happiness begins.
吾輩は決して無理強いはしない、やるもやらぬもおまえ次第だ
I will never force you. Whether you do it or not is up to you.
では締め括りに吾輩の波動を送る 3、2、1...
Now, to conclude, I shall send you my energy wave. 3, 2, 1...
今だ！
Now!
おまえのライブ運は上昇している
Your luck regarding live shows is rising.
このままライブを見続けるのだ
Keep watching this live stream.
甘い夢見て 心までラ・ラ・プラ・プラ・プラ 餌付けて
Dreaming sweet dreams, baiting my very heart with La-la-pla-pla-pla.
ただ深い微睡みの 喉にラ・ラ・プラ・プラ・プラ 混ざり合って
Blending into a deep slumber, down the throat with La-la-pla-pla-pla.
ぐるるるる
Grrr rrrr rr.
一つ二つ 宵闇にラ・ラ・プラ・プラ・プラ 蕩けて
One, two, melting into the twilight with La-la-pla-pla-pla.
ただ熱いその命さえ ラ・ラ・プラ・プラ・プラ 飲まれてさ
Even that hot life itself is swallowed up by La-la-pla-pla-pla.
ぐるるるる
Grrr rrrr rr.
名・UFO・UFO ビ・ア・UFO 前世善の運命委ねて
Mei-UFO-UFO, be-a-UFO, entrusting the fate of my past life's goodness.
アイ・UFO・UFO ビ・ア・UFO...
Ai-UFO-UFO, be-a-UFO...
...ろころ その身捧げ 闇通わせ まわりまわる世界
...offering this body, making the darkness flow, the world that turns and turns.
Hello Yes My DARKNESS
括目！ 暗黒！ 悪！ 悪！
Look closely! Darkness! Evil! Evil!
Hello Yes My DARKNESS
あしたから見えぬ獄
A hell unseen from tomorrow
ぐるるる... ほら抱きしめて
Grrr... Look, hold me tight
DARKNESS
がるるる... ほら食べちゃって
Garrr... Look, eat it up
DARKNESS
甘い夢見て 常闇で ラブラブラブ 焼き付けて
Dreaming a sweet dream in eternal darkness, sear it in, Lap-Lap-Lap
そばで笑いかける 悪魔の声が鳴り響いて
The voice of the demon laughing by my side resounds
ぐるるる...
Grrr...
UFO UFO BE A UFO
奔放！ 奔放！ 絡めとられて
Wild! Wild! Entrapped and taken
I FOR YOU FOR BE I YOU FOR
ろころ その響きさえ 闇通わせ
...rokoro, even that sound makes the darkness flow
黒く溶き染めあげ やがて混ざる世界
Dissolving and staining black, a world that will soon mix together
主観！ 彩！ 濁。 濁。 濁。 溶け込む 満たしてく
Subjectivity! Color! Muddy. Muddy. Muddy. Dissolving, filling up
絶対絶唱 DARKNESS ハーモニー交わる世界
Absolute Vocalization DARKNESS, a world where harmony intersects
DARKNESS
括目！ 暗黒！ 悪！ 悪！
Look closely! Darkness! Evil! Evil!
絶対絶唱 DARKNESS
Absolute Vocalization DARKNESS
あした...
Tomorrow...
ぐるるる... ほら抱きしめて DARKNESS
Grrr... Look, hold me tight DARKNESS
がるるる... ほら食べちゃって DARKNESS
Garrr... Look, eat it up DARKNESS
テレスコープごしの感情 ロッカーに全部詰め込んだ
Emotions through the telescope, I stuffed them all into a locker
踊ってない夜を知らない 踊ってない夜が気に入らない
I don't know a night without dancing, I don't like a night without dancing
気に入らない夜なんて もう僕は知らない
I don't care anymore about a night I don't like
-ERROR 作詞・作曲：niki
-ERROR Lyrics/Composition: niki
見えるこの目の涙 命の色に滲んでいる
The tears visible in these eyes are blurring into the color of life
何を求めて嘲笑った？ 問いかけて 潰れて
What were you seeking when you sneered? Asking questions, being crushed
青と赤と白混ざる この世の中で叫んでいる
Blue and red and white mix together, screaming in this world
何を求めて歩いた？ 追いかけて 疲れて
What were you seeking as you walked? Chasing, getting tired
どのくらい？ 異常？
How much? Abnormal?
壊れているの？
Am I broken?
壊れているよ
I am broken.
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to
君に見えてる？
Can you see it?
夢のように 最後を
Like a dream, the end...
言葉が詰まるよ
The words are getting stuck
ERROR
遠い日のこと 淡い光が空に溢れている
Things from a distant day, a faint light is overflowing in the sky
何を選んで並べた？ 涙を重ねて
What did you choose and line up? Piling up the tears
浮かぶその体 意識の中 溶けて滲んでしまう
That floating body, dissolving and blurring within my consciousness
何を見つけて比べた？ 悲しくて 忘れて
What did you find and compare? Being sad, forgetting
どのくらい？ 異常？
How much? Abnormal?
歪んでいるの？
Am I distorted?
歪んでいるよ
I am distorted.
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to
夢を見ている
I'm dreaming
想い沁みる 最後を
Feelings soaking in, the end...
言葉が詰まるよ
The words are getting stuck
ERROR
与えることも失うことも 忘れることもできないの
I can't give, I can't lose, and I can't even forget
暴れ出すこのエラー
This error that's running wild
殺して笑う僕がまたエラー
Me, who kills and laughs, is another error
壊して 嫌だ
Break it... no
壊して 死ぬの
Break it... will I die?
それでも涙 痛い 痛い
Even so, the tears... it hurts, it hurts
君に届いたの？
Did it reach you?
歌う声に最後の...
To my singing voice, the last...
言葉並べても
Even if I line up the words
重なる色 滲んで
The overlapping colors blur
壊れているの？
Is it broken?
壊れているよ
It is broken
それでも息を したい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to
君に見えてたの？
Could you see it?
夢のように最後の...
Like a dream, the last...
言葉も詰まるよ
Even the words get stuck
エラー
Error
本日は...
Today...
...皆様、ラプラス・ダークネス生誕祭をご覧いただき...
...everyone, thank you for watching the La+ Darknesss Birthday Celebration...
...ありがとうございます。
...thank you very much.
今回、ホロライブのゲストと一緒に歌っていないことについて一言。
A word about not singing with Hololive guests this time.
うああああー、皆さんには分からないでしょうね！
Uwaaaa, you guys probably don't understand!
このホロライブを！
This Hololive!
買いたい！その一心で！
I want to buy it! With that single-mindedness!
どうしても次の曲ゲスト呼びたくて！
I really wanted to invite guests for the next song!
いろんな人呼びたいって、声かけまくってたらゲストの人数とか凄いことになって！
I kept asking around because I wanted to invite all kinds of people, and the number of guests became crazy!
他のゲストが呼べなくなったんですー！
I couldn't invite any other guests!
というわけで、次の曲のゲストすごいです。
So, the guests for the next song are amazing.
シュガーソングとビターステップ / 作詞・作曲：田淵智也
Sugar Song and Bitter Step / Lyrics & Composition: Tomoya Tabuchi
八雲べに / ラプラス・ダークネス / 荒咬オウガ / 赤見かるび / 96猫
Yakumo Beni / La+ Darknesss / Aragami Oga / Akami Karubi / 96neko
dtto. / こぼ・かなえる / 橙汰つな / rurudo / 天鬼ぷるる / 夕刻ロベル
dtto. / Kobo Kanaeru / Touta Tsuna / rurudo / Amaki Pururu / Yukoku Roberu
超天変地異みたいな狂騒にも慣れて
Getting used to the uproar like a super natural disaster
こんなに日常平和と見間違い
Mistaking it for peaceful daily life like this
ランブリングコースター揺さぶられながら
While being shaken by the Rambling Coaster
見失えないものは何だ
What is it that I can't lose sight of?
平等性原理主義の概念に飲まれて
Swallowed by the concept of egalitarian fundamentalism
心までがまるでエトセトラ
Even my heart is just like 'et cetera'
大嫌い 大好き ちゃんと喋らなきゃ
Hate it, love it, I have to speak properly
人形とさして変わらないし
I'm not much different from a doll
宵街を行く人だかりは
The crowds walking through the evening streets
嬉しそうだったり 寂しそうだったり
Look happy or lonely
コントラストが五線を飛び回り
The contrast flies around the staff
歌とリズムになれ
Become the song and rhythm
ママレード＆シュガーソング ピーナッツ＆ビターステップ
Marmalade & Sugar Song, Peanuts & Bitter Step
甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
It's sweet and bitter, and my head feels like it's spinning
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう
Let's keep the party going towards the south-southwest
世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になる
It will be a night that will surprise the whole world
I feel 上々 連鎖してリフレクト
I feel top-notch, chain and reflect
蓋然性合理主義の正誤に飲まれて
Swallowed by the right and wrong of probabilistic rationalism
僕らの音楽は道具になり下がり
Our music has degenerated into a tool
こっち向いてよ 背を向けないでよ
Look over here, don't turn your back
それは正論にならないけど
That won't become a sound argument, but
死のその後で
After death
高鳴り出す人が　泣き出してしまう人が
People who get excited, people who start crying
多分同じだろう
They're probably the same
でも言葉にしようものなら
But if you were to put it into words
稚拙が極まれり
It would be the height of clumsiness
最高だって、シュガーソング　幸せだって、ビターステップ
It's the best, sugar song. It's happiness, bitter step.
死ねない理由をそこに映し出せ
Project the reasons you can't die right there
おしげなく、こそばゆくて、明日はくちゃげど
Without hesitation, it's ticklish, even if tomorrow is a mess
脳内天気予報のアップデートを果たしたなら
Once you've updated your internal weather forecast
Someday 狂騒外、気を逸らしても
Someday, even if you turn your eyes away from the frenzy
Someday 0、2、右が見えなくなっても
Someday, even if you can no longer see zero, two, or the right
平気だって鳴らし続けることだけが
Just continuing to ring out that everything's okay
僕たちを僕たちたらしめる証明になるQED
Will be the proof that makes us who we are, Q.E.D.
マバレだって、シュガーソング　生きてく理由をそこに映し出せ
Even if it's dizzying, sugar song. Project the reasons you live right there.
ほくほくと、ほほえむ、その距離はおかし、世界中を驚かせ続けよう
Smiling warmly, that distance is strange, let's keep surprising the whole world.
マバレだって、シュガーソング　ピーナッツ＆ビターステップ、甘くて苦くて目が回りそうです
Even if it's dizzying, sugar song. Peanuts & bitter step, it's so sweet and bitter that I feel dizzy.
南南西を目指してパーティを続けよう、世界中を驚かせてしまう夜になれ
Let's keep the party going towards the south-southwest, let it be a night that surprises the whole world.
I feel 頂上現象になっていくよ、サッテ、イチナンサッテマタイッキョ
I feel it's becoming a peak phenomenon, now, one trouble follows another.
サッテ、イチナンサッテマタイッキョ
Now, one trouble follows another.
You got the happiness, phrase and the melody.
え、ラプラス・ダークネスってオリ曲3曲しかないの？
Wait, La+ Darkness only has three original songs?
やっぱ、期待しちゃダメじゃない？新曲なんて出すわけないんだから
I knew it, we shouldn't get our hopes up. There's no way she's releasing a new song.
ラプラス・ダークネスなんて当てにしちゃダメだよ。ん。
You can't rely on someone like La+ Darkness. Yeah.
え、新曲出るの？
What, a new song is coming out?
しかもDECO*27さんなの！？
And it's by DECO*27?!
タイトル？
The title?
「バグラブ」？
“Bug Love”?
それって・・・つまり自己防衛？
Does that... mean self-defense?
この後披露するの？
Is she performing it after this?
これ見ないとダメじゃない？ん。
We have to watch this, don't we? Yeah.
この後見逃しちゃダメだよ。ん。
Don't miss what's coming next. Yeah.
つまり自己防衛？
So, self-defense?
ん。
Yeah.
やっぱりラプレスハッピーじゃん
It's La+ Happy after all.
あーまさか これってまさか 好きってやつか どんなんか知らないけど
Oh, could it be? Is this "love"? I don't know what it's like, but...
はてなって火花 バチってなるの 鈍感でいられたらなあ
Sparks of question marks go pop! I wish I could just stay oblivious.
あーこんなはずじゃ とんだ恥じゃ 残念の始まりじゃ
Oh, it wasn't supposed to be like this. What a total embarrassment. It's the beginning of the end.
あーとんでも事案 ハートの治安 曖昧でお仕舞いじゃん
Oh, what a crazy situation. The peace of my heart is gone. It's all over with this ambiguity.
気になって 気にしないとこ 気になるとこ
I'm curious. The things I try not to care about, the things I end up caring about.
気まずくて きみやむじゃない
It's awkward. You're not going to stop, are you?
バグってるラブ あたしなんですか？やだよがっかりラブ デビューベイビーじゃん
Bugged love, is it me? No way, it's a disappointing love debut, baby.
痛だけの気持ち 最悪の見込み 好きって認めなね
Just painful feelings, the worst outlook. Don't admit you like it.
バグってるラブ あたしなんかじゃない そうだやっぱりラプレスハッピーじゃん
Bugged love, it's not me. That's right, it's La+ Happy after all.
期待なんてなしな あっちけバリア 好きってならないでねの
Don't have any expectations. Go away, barrier! Don't fall in love, okay?
距離感です
It's the distance.
正直あたしは終わった 何しようがどうも モヤモヤが消えない
Honestly, I'm done. No matter what I do, this feeling won't go away.
呆然ただ笑った いつも通りロンリー 息をしたいのに
I just laughed in a daze. Lonely as always, even though I want to breathe.
意地張っていじけるとかいじらしいから
Being stubborn and sulking is so pathetic.
恋って冗談じゃない？
Isn't love just a joke?
恋路って異常なんじゃない？
Isn't the path of love abnormal?
バババ バグラブ
Ba-ba-ba Bug Love
あたしなんですか？
Is it me?
やだよ がっかり
Oh no, disappointment
ラブデビューベイビーじゃん
It's a love debut, baby
未体験のIFに
To an unexperienced IF,
解釈ブレ気味
interpretations are shaking.
好きって好きじゃないわ
Loving isn't really loving.
バババ バグラブ
Ba-ba-ba Bug Love
あたしなんかじゃない
It's not someone like me.
そうだ やっぱり
That's right, as I thought,
ラブレスハッピーじゃん
it's loveless happy.
意外すぎる味が
A flavor too unexpected
飲み込めないや
I can't swallow.
好きってまずいんだね
Love tastes bad, doesn't it?
こうやって枯れてくことが 想いの反動なら
If withering away like this is a reaction to my feelings,
はじめから言って 知っておきたいじゃん
I'd want to know if you'd told me from the start.
それってちょっと卑怯じゃん
That's a bit unfair, isn't it?
きみのことを気になることも 回避できたかもじゃん
I might have even been able to avoid falling for you.
バババ バグラブ
Ba-ba-ba Bug Love
あたしなんですか？
Is it me?
やだよ がっかり
Oh no, disappointment
ラブデビューベイビーじゃん
It's a love debut, baby
痛いだけの気持ち
A feeling that only hurts,
最悪の飲み込み
the worst thing to swallow.
好きって認めないね
You won't admit it's love.
バババ バグラブ
Ba-ba-ba Bug Love
あたしなんかじゃない
It's not someone like me.
そうだ やっぱり
That's right, as I thought,
ラブレスハッピーじゃん
it's loveless happy.
期待なんてなしな
No expectations here,
あっちけバリア
stay away barrier.
好きってならないね の距離感で
With a distance that won't let it become love,
気になって 気にしないと 気になるから
Because if I try not to care, I end up caring even more,
いつだって逃げられるような そんな距離感で
with a distance that allows me to run away anytime,
やっぱりラブレスハッピーじゃん
it really is loveless happy.
はぁ... はぁ...
Haah... haah...
と、いうわけで
So, with that out of the way,
なんとオリジナル曲が出るよー！
original songs are coming out!
あと 自己防衛おじさんが言ってた通り
And just like the self-defense uncle said,
DECO*27さんが作ってくれたよ！
DECO*27-san wrote them for me!
ビズラ！ありがとね！
Vizla! Thank you!
振付もオリジナルなんだけど
The choreography is also original.
どうでしたか？
How was it?
毎年ね、1曲ずつ作っていきたいんだけど
I want to make one song every year...
あ！「クライ」はタイアップ曲だから
Ah! 'Cry' is a tie-up song,
ノーカンで！
so it doesn't count!
あれね、でも、思ったより人気だったから
That one, well, it was more popular than I expected,
今回みんながこうやって見れるライブで初めて披露したよ！
so I performed it for the first time in a live stream like this!
ライブでやるのは2回目！2回目だよー！
It's the second time doing it live! The second time!
えーとね、「バグラブ」はミュージックビデオも公開するから絶対見てね！
And, the 'Bug Love' music video will be out too, so you must watch it!
そして今年は、もしかしたら…おっと！
And this year, maybe... oops!
というわけで、この後は、あれですよ
So, after this, we have that thing,
グッズ情報だよー！
merchandise information!
なんと今回はCMがあるよー！
Believe it or not, there's a CM this time!
どうぞ！
Here it is!
誕生日記念 2025
Birthday Commemoration 2025
これどんな感じだ？
What's this one like?
しゃべる！
It talks!
しゃべった！
It talked!
しゃべる！
It talks!
ボイスキーホルダー 私服衣装ver.
Voice Keychain (Casual Clothes ver.)
ラプラスさんのグッズで、今回Tシャツが出るそうなんですが
I heard a T-shirt is being released as part of La+-san's goods.
まことに遺憾です。残念です。
It's truly regrettable. Disappointing.
いいTシャツ着てんじゃんかよ。プルルだろ、それ。
You're wearing a nice T-shirt there. That's a Plulu one, right?
バキバキラブ様です。
It's Bakibaki Love-sama.
ラプラスさんの生誕グッズが、カラスのニット帽らしいんですが
I hear La+-san's birthday goods include a crow knit hat.
世界的なアイドルですもんね。
She's a world-class idol, after all.
乗るしかないですよね、このビッグウェーブに。
I have no choice but to ride this big wave.
はい、CMでしたー！
Yes, that was the CM!
どうだった？
How was it?
え？よく分からない？
Eh? You don't really get it?
しょうがないな、もう。
Oh, for goodness sake.
じゃあ詳細を見せてあげましょう。こちら！
Then I'll show you the details. Here!
ラプラス・ダークネス 誕生日記念 2025
La+ Darknesss Birthday Commemoration 2025
フルセット こんな感じで
The full set looks like this...
それでは一つずつ内容も見ていきましょう。
Now, let's look at the items one by one.
まずはこちら！
First is this!
Tシャツだよー！
It's the T-shirt!
イラストは、ちょぼらうにょぽみ先生が書いてくれたよ！
The illustration was drawn by Choboraunyopomi-sensei!
言えたー！可愛いでしょ？
I said it! Isn't it cute?
いっぱい着てね。
Please wear it a lot.
服は何枚あっても困りませんからね、
You can never have too many clothes,
いっぱい着てください。
so please wear it a lot.
そして続いてはこちら、ジャン！
And next is this, ta-da!
ボイスキーホルダー私服衣装バージョンということでですね、
The Voice Keyholder Private Clothes Version!
去年も思ってたよりめちゃくちゃ大人気だった我が輩のボイスキーホルダーで、
Last year, my voice keyholder was way more popular than I expected.
もうみんな「また売って、また売って」って言われたから、
Everyone kept asking, "Please sell it again, please sell it again!"
えーしょうがないなあと思ってまた出すことにしました。
So I thought, "Oh well, I guess I have to," and decided to release it again.
イラスト...イラストは今回も、しろこ先生に描いてもらっただぞ、
The illustration... the illustration was drawn by Shiroko-sensei this time too!
待って間違えた。
Wait, I messed up the wording.
はい、どんなボイスが入ってるかお楽しみに。
Anyway, look forward to hearing what kind of voices are included.
お次はこちら。
Next is this.
カラスのニット帽！
The Crow Knit Hat!
ということで我が輩にいつもつきまとってるカラスの、えーモチーフが入った、
This is a knit hat featuring the motif...
顔か、顔が入ったニット帽です。
well, the face of the crow that's always following me around.
はい、これ目出し帽になるんですけど、
Yes, this can be worn as a balaclava,
ここ目だけ見えてるやつ。
where only your eyes are visible.
えーこれはちょっと、イベントとかにつけていくと防犯上急なんで、
Um, wearing this to events might be a bit of a security concern,
えーイベントに行く時は顔出しで、
so please show your face when you're at events,
家でつける時はこの目出し帽で、つけてね。
and use it as a balaclava when you're at home.
暖かいよ。
It's warm!
そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here is the Full Set purchase bonus!
直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入り、
A postcard with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped replica signature,
ちょぼらうにょぽみ先生の描き下ろしポストカードです。
illustrated by Choboraunyopomi-sensei.
なんと今回は、数量限定じゃないです。
For this one, it's not a limited quantity!
頑張っていっぱい書きます。さようなら我が輩のお手手。
I'll do my best to write a lot of them. Goodbye, my hands.
そして、さらにフルセットを購入した方には、
Furthermore, those who purchase the full set will receive
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが1枚付いてくるよ。ジャン！
one card that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME. Ta-da!
同梱するカードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入されたお客様のみ対象となります。
The included card is only available to customers who purchase from the hololive production official shop.
えーとね、特典につくのは、ゲームで1枚だけ使用できて、
Um, the bonus card is a key card that can be used in the game
推しホロメンをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。
to show off your favorite hololive member, an "Oshi Holomen Card."
はい、カードの詳細や遊び方については、
Yes, please check the official hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME website
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEの公式ホームページで確認してください。
for card details and how to play.
えーこのカードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご了承ください。
Please note that this card is only available in Japanese.
そして、我が輩がいる、キュリアスユニバースも、
And "Curious Universe," which I'm in,
6月20日、来月発売されるので、一緒に使ってね。
will also be released on June 20th, next month, so please use it together!
はい、ということで。グッズもよろしく。
All right, then. Please check out the merch.
はぁー、今回はね、ゲストが盛りだくさんだったね。
Phew, we had so many guests this time.
えーといろんな振り返りとかはまた配信で話すかもしれないから、
Well, I might talk more about various highlights in another stream later,
その時お楽しみに。
so look forward to that.
バイバーイ、バイバイバイバーイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye-bye-bye!
インターネットでありがとう
Thank you on the internet